Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/sarag-162327124 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Hospitals Meditech

Epic Systems

Certifications

ACLS

BLS

NIHSS

Sara Guilliams

Travel RN

Roanoke, Virginia

Summary

I am currently a critical care travel nurse. I have worked contracts as float ICU, MICU, SICU, CPICU. Previous experiences include working on the Surgical Intensive Care Unit at Lewis Gale Medical Center where I cared for critically ill patients directly post-operative. I am also trained to perform continuous renal replacement therapy with Nx stage equipment. Other previous experience includes working on the Medical Progressive Care Unit. I am current in NIHSS, ACLS and BLS.

Experience

travel rn

Travel RN

September 2017 - Present (2 years 10 months)

Lewis Gale Medical Center

2 years 4 months

Critical Care RN

July 2016 - October 2017 (1 year 4 months)

Surgical Intensive Care Unit

RN

July 2015 - July 2016 (1 year 1 month)

Medical Progressive Care Unit

Roanoke Memorial Hospital

Clinical Associate

July 2013 - June 2015 (2 years)

Education

Jefferson College of Health Sciences

Bachelor of Science (B.S.), Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse \cdot (2014 - 2015)

Radford University

Bachelor of Science (B.S.), Nutrition and Dietetics · (2006 - 2010)